Bá Quang Trần

Product Engineer



PERSONAL INFORMATION

© Male

20-05-2002

© 0866407529

O Nguyet Duc, Yen Lac, Vinh Phuc

LANGUAGES

English



SKILLS

- Quick learning and perception skills
- Good listening and communication skills
- Teamwork skills

SOFTWARE

Office Informatics



Programming



OBJECTIVE

I want to use all my knowledge and skills to devote myself to the company, helping me to increasingly fulfill the assigned work. I will use my personal experience to quickly adapt and get along with colleagues in the new environment.

WORK EXPERIENCE

07-2023 - 09-2023 | MULTI-TALENTED EMPLOYEE CANON HUNG YEN

Receive work from the Technical Manager, process production according to the plan.

- Work with the production manufacturing department to complete the product.
- Get acquainted with the professional working environment.
- Learn about automation, many modern machines...
- Complete the work well during the working time at the company.

01-2024 - 03-2024 | TECHNICAL STAFF COMPAL VINH PHUC

Work in the technical department.

- Learn about the company's products and services.
- Check and operate machinery to keep the production line operating.
- Work with the production department manufacture and repair products.
- Learn about many modern automatic machines
- Complete tasks well during the working time at the company

EDUCATION

10-2020 - 06-2024 | HANOI UNIVERSITY OF INDUSTRY

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER ENGINEERING

TECHNOLOGY

Degree classification: Good